(Penny:)I can't believe Sheldon was
gonna ask Amy to marry him.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I know.
I also can't believe
(Leonard:)he watched what we did
on that couch
(Leonard:)and still sits on it.
Yeah.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello.
(Leonard:)Hey, buddy.
How you doing?
(Sheldon:)Better.
(Sheldon:)Did Wil and Adam leave?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Do you think they're
going to put my outburst
(Sheldon:)in the documentary?
(Penny:)Definitely.
Oh, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Well, there's no point
in dwelling on it.
(Sheldon:)As the Vulcans say,
“Kup-fun-tor
ha'kiv na'ish Du stau.”
(Penny:)Do you know what that means?
No.
(Penny:)Are you telling the truth?
Nirsh.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is ridiculous.
Being upset about Amy
(Howard:)all the time
isn't accomplishing anything.
(Sheldon:)If I want to resolve
this situation,
(Sheldon:)then I need to take action.
(Penny:)What are you gonna do?
I'm going to find her
(Sheldon:)and ask her to marry me.
(Sheldon:)And if she says yes,
we can put this behind us
(Sheldon:)and resume our relationship.
(Sheldon:)And if she says no...
(Sheldon:)well, then
she can just ponfo miran.